FIRST REPORTER
The head of SETI will give a full press conference
Today in the wake of the verified and authentic
non-terrestrial transmission
coming from just beyond the asteroid
belt in our solar system.
SECOND REPORTER
Contact with the colony on Mars will
be re-established and have nothing to
do with the impending
arrival of the mysterious aliens.
THIRD REPORTER
The McCulloch space station
has just been destroyed.
[Overlapping News Reports]
FIRST REPORTER
Paris, Peking, Reykjavik, and Tokyo
head the list of recently devastated cities.
[Overlapping News Reports]
FOURTH REPORTER
And the UA President gave the uplifting farewell
speech as these brave soldiers took
the fight to the Strogg's home planet.
We, the rest of humanity, wish
them luck and Godspeed as well.
[Explosion]
RED LEADER
Mother Goose, Mother Goose,
this is Red Leader Alpha Charlie 417.
MOTHER GOOSE
Gotcha on the scope Red Leader.
See that big bad dust ball up ahead?
RED LEADER
Roger that Mother Goose.
Target is acquired.
Heading towards that
point, X-Ray Lima Seven.
COMMAND
Deployment is green
for Alpha, Bravo...
FIRST CREW
There's [unintelligible] surface
surface EZ still looks clean...
[Overlapping Command Ship Checks]
SECOND CREW
The pitch check confirmed.
SERGEANT
[Unintelligible] shit
Marines are dangerous!
FIRST LAUNCH CREW
Let the sky divide.
SECOND LAUNCH CREW
Negative! His shit's wire.
Wake his ass up.
THIRD LAUNCH CREW
Alright Bitterman, you are
in the green and ready to go.
OTHER MARINE
Yeeeehaaaaaa
BITTERMAN
Shit! What was that?
Command, I got a problem here.
Some cowboy clipped
me on the way in man.
Pressures are at 50% and dropping.
COMMAND
Copy Bitterman. Your stats are
nominal but proceed to designated target LZ.
We'll see what we
can... holy shit! Bitterman!
Bitterman! What the hell is going on?
We just lost a third of the platoon
just as they crashed sector Niner X-ray.
We got a visual on any AA discharge?
BITTERMAN
Negative command, I'm approaching
Niner X-Ray right now.
And there's no heat from the ground.
OTHER MARINE
They're coming at me from all angles!
BITTERMAN
I just crossed the board
around 10 seconds ago.
COMMAND
Damn it! They've got a
little freaky EMP down there.
Getting clipped just
saved your ass marine.
I just lost all readings
for the rest of the platoon.
Try and get to the primary LZ and rendezvous
with any other squad leaders you can find.
BITTERMAN
Shit! Just overshot LZ, Command.
Command, you copy?
Christ, this thing is a brick! I have no
flight control. Repeat! No flight control!
I'm south of the LZ, nearing
the southern structure!
Ready for crash landing!
Command! [signal breaking]
Copy?
Command, come in!
I have no flight control!
[Explosion]