STEPCHILD
This is Private Stepchild calling to
Deimos. Stepchild calling to Deimos.
I've planted the charges
on the gravity well generator.
Inform all remaining ground
troops to evacuate the area.
Copy that, Stepchild.
Now get out of there.
DEIMOS
Roger. Stepchild out.
SECURITY COMPUTER
Security breach detected?
You are not clear for takeoff.
STEPCHILD
Shit! I'm not going to make it!
[Explosion]
STEPCHILD
Stepchild to Deimos. Did it work?
DEIMOS
Hell yes it worked, Private.
We're reporting total destruction
of primary target and huge secondary chain
reaction explosions all
across the planet's surface.
Nothing's living on that rock.
STEPCHILD
What about the others?
DEIMOS
There aren't that many
left to retrieve, Stepchild.
You're one of the lucky few that
made it out of that inferno in one piece.
STEPCHILD
Let's get the hell out of here.
[Deimos Bay Doors Closing]