SERGEANT HOSS
Affirmative Deimos, Zulu Section 5
is clear and away. Sergeant Hoss out.
Alright marines, haul your sorry asses into formation.
Corporals Swampy and Wooley will take point position.
Let's do this by the numbers folks, we
don't want any fender benders out here.
DEIMOS
Keep an eye on those inertial
dampers or you'll splash on impact.
COMMAND CREW
Fifth section, start your status check.
SHORT PUNCH
Short Punch, check!
GARFUNKEL
Garfunkel, check.
BLENDER
Blender, check.
GERONIMO
Geronimo, check.
ZOR
Zor, check.
ROD
Rod, check.
STEPCHILD
Stepchild, check.
DEIMOS
Attention all capital ships.
Deployment phase complete.
Fall back from orbit,
wait for retrieval.
SERGEANT HOSS
Outstanding. Good luck
marines, see you on the ground.
GROUP LEADER
Rod, get your ass back in line.
ROD
I gotta touch ground,
Drops always [unintelligible] me bro.
[Explosion]
GARFUNKEL
Shit, what the hell was that?
SHORT PUNCH
Heads up y'all, I'm
breaking formation. Yeehaw!
ZOR
Picking up a big ass power surge.
GARFUNKEL
Why aren't the capital
ships bugging out?
DEIMOS
Something's very wrong here.
Power generators increasing
the planet's gravitation.
MARINE PILOT
Damn it, [unintelligible]
DEIMOS
Lock-on to that power source and fire
everything we have at it. [unintelligible] this channel.
GERONIMO
We've got company. At least thirteen
Strogg fighters verified.
STEPCHILD
Just flew over us.
BLENDER
We'll never make the
LZ. We're screwed!
STEPCHILD
Let's dust them.
DEIMOS
Attention all crew, we
are unable to break orbit.
They've somehow increased
the planet's gravitational pull.
Locate the disabled
generator at all costs.
We'll provide cover
fire to clear your LZ.
SERGEANT HOSS
You heard the man, we'll have
our chance to take it down.
Start for final approaches.
STEPCHILD
Got one on your tail
sir.  It's following us in.
[Explosion]
STEPCHILD
Too late to bail, I'm going in.